Faculty of Science fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
- Faculty committee records, 1966 - 1995; F-24-3; 2.68 m of textual records
  - Faculty Extended Studies Diploma Advisory Committee, 1981; F-24-3-20; 1 cm of textual records
    - Correspondence, 1981; F-24-3-20-0-1 (Archival box - standard 24-53)
      Creator's original file classification code: F-1-16.
  - Faculty of Science Safety Committee, 1972 - 1994; F-24-3-21; 11 cm of textual records
    - Correspondence, minutes and reports, 1972 - 1974; F-24-3-21-0-1 (Archival box - standard 24-53)
      Creator's original file classification code: F-1-6.
    - WCB Inspections, 1981 - 1985; F-24-3-21-0-2 (Archival box - standard 24-53)
      Creator's original file classification code: 4.13.
    - Correspondence, minutes and reports, vol. 1, 1981 - 1994; F-24-3-21-0-3 (Archival box - standard 24-53)
    - Correspondence, minutes and reports, vol. 2, 1981 - 1994; F-24-3-21-0-4 (Archival box - standard 24-53)
    - Correspondence, minutes and reports, vol. 3, 1981 - 1994; F-24-3-21-0-5 (Archival box - standard 24-54)
    - Correspondence, minutes and reports, vol. 4, 1981 - 1994; F-24-3-21-0-6 (Archival box - standard 24-54)
    - Correspondence, minutes and reports, vol. 5, 1981 - 1994; F-24-3-21-0-7 (Archival box - standard 24-54)
    - Correspondence, minutes and reports, vol. 6, 1981 - 1994; F-24-3-21-0-8 (Archival box - standard 24-54)
    - Correspondence, minutes and reports, vol. 7, 1981 - 1994; F-24-3-21-0-9 (Archival box - standard 24-54)
- Faculty publications, 1965 - 2000; F-24-4; 20 cm of textual records
  Series consists of publications produced by the Faculty of Science. Records include Faculty of Science Who's Who booklets, weekly faculty newsletters and safety bulletins, workshop and conference programs, LAMBDA - the SFU Science Undergrad Journal, Albert Einstein Centennial Lecture series posters, the Department of Biology Safety Manual, curriculum program guides, institute brochures, and one calendar.
  The publications found in this series were acquired by the Archives from a variety of undocumented sources. Although the original accession of Faculty of Science records contained a number of departmental publications, most of the publications were collected by Archives staff as part of an artificial university-wide periodicals collection and then processed as part of the fonds.
  For Annual Reports (1980-2000) produced by the Faculty of Science please see sub-series F-24-1-4.
  - Purple Period newsletter, 1965; F-24-4-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 24-54)
  - Measures of Excellence Series, [197-?]; F-24-4-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 24-54)
  - Frontiers of Science, [197-?]; F-24-4-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 24-54)
  - Pamphlets and reports, [197-?]; F-24-4-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 24-54)
  - Faculty of Science Research Directory, 1970; F-24-4-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 24-54)
  - Faculty of Science First Year Courses, 1970 - 1971; F-24-4-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 24-54)
  - Statesmen of Science Lecture series, 1970 - 1973; F-24-4-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 24-54)
  - Faculty of Science Newsletter, 1973 - 1976; F-24-4-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 24-56)
  - LAMBDA - SFU Science Undergrad Journal, 1974 - 1975; F-24-4-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 24-56)
  - Department of Chemistry publications, 1979 - 1984; F-24-4-0-0-10 (Archival box - standard 24-56)
  - Albert Einstein Centennial Lecture Series, 1980 - 1983; F-24-4-0-0-11 (Archival box - standard 24-56)
  - Department of Biology publications, 1980 - 1986; F-24-4-0-0-12 (Archival box - standard 24-56)
  - Faculty of Science Who's Who, 1981; F-24-4-0-0-13 (Archival box - standard 24-56)
  - Faculty of Science Safety Bulletin, 1982 - 1986; F-24-4-0-0-14 (Archival box - standard 24-56)
  - Department of Physics publications, 1984 - 1991; F-24-4-0-0-15 (Archival box - standard 24-56)
  - Department of Biology Safety Manual, 1985; F-24-4-0-0-16 (Archival box - standard 24-56)
  - Sciences at SFU, 1986; F-24-4-0-0-17 (Archival box - standard 24-56)
  - Sciences at SFU, 1988; F-24-4-0-0-18 (Archival box - standard 24-56)
  - Catalyst '90 conference program, 1990; F-24-4-0-0-19 (Archival box - standard 24-56)
  - Faculty of Science Who's Who, vol. 1, 1991; F-24-4-0-0-20 (Archival box - standard 24-56)
  - Faculty of Science Who's Who, vol. 2, 1991; F-24-4-0-0-21 (Archival box - standard 24-56)
  - Catalyst '93 conference program, 1993; F-24-4-0-0-22 (Archival box - standard 24-56)
  - Science and Tech Open House poster, 1996; F-24-4-0-0-23 (Archival box - standard 24-56)
  - Continuing Studies in Science Institute, 1996; F-24-4-0-0-24 (Archival box - standard 24-56)
  - Faculty of Science calendar, 2000; F-24-4-0-0-25 (Archival box - standard 24-56)
- Financial records, 1993 - 1996; F-24-5; 28 cm of textual records
  Series consists of records relating to the financial operation of the Faculty of Science and includes administration of the faculty budget, individual departmental budgets, and operating budgets for teaching assistants and sessional instructors. Records include correspondence, budgets, statistics, reports and financial working papers.
  - Operating budget - Faculty, 1993 - 1994; F-24-5-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 24-57)
  - Operating budget - TA, vol. 1, 1993 - 1994; F-24-5-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 24-57)
  - Operating budget - TA, vol. 2, 1993 - 1994; F-24-5-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 24-57)
  - Operating budget - CFL and Sessional, 1993 - 1994; F-24-5-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 24-57)
  - Faculty budget, vol. 1, 1993 - 1994; F-24-5-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 24-57)
  - Faculty budget, vol. 2, 1993 - 1994; F-24-5-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 24-57)
  - Faculty budget, vol. 3, 1993 - 1994; F-24-5-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 24-58)
  - Operating budget, 1994 - 1995; F-24-5-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 24-58)
  - Faculty budget, 1994 - 1995; F-24-5-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 24-58)
  - Departmental budget, vol. 1, 1994 - 1995; F-24-5-0-0-10 (Archival box - standard 24-58)
  - Departmental budget, vol. 2, 1994 - 1995; F-24-5-0-0-11 (Archival box - standard 24-58)
  - Faculty budget, vol. 1, 1995 - 1996; F-24-5-0-0-12 (Archival box - standard 24-58)
  - Faculty budget, vol. 2, 1995 - 1996; F-24-5-0-0-13 (Archival box - standard 24-58)
  - Operating budget, 1995 - 1996; F-24-5-0-0-14 (Archival box - standard 24-59)
  - Departmental budget, 1995 - 1996; F-24-5-0-0-15 (Archival box - standard 24-59)